NICOLAI B. THOMSEN

DATA SCIENCE STUDENT BUSINESS ANALYST & RESEARCH ASSISTANT

PROFILE

Since a start in IT-based startups I've worked with business development, IT project management, IT consultancy and data analytics. In 2020, I'm focusing on enhancing my data science capabilities, particularly within machine learning, statistical principles and functional programming for data analysis.

EXPERIENCE

BUSINESS ANALYST

Deloitte | Tech, Strategy & Transformation | Sept. 2019 -

- Deliverables within IT strategy, finance and IT op. models
- Big Data & AA community | Chatbot community
- Development / configuration of chatbot(s)

NLP RESEARCH ASSISTANT

CBS | Dept. of Mgmt., Society & Comms. | Sept. 2019 -

- ML-based pattern detection in natural language
- Data cleansing, data wrangling, regex

CRM QUALITY ASSESSMENT MANAGER

Simply | STARTUP | 2016 – 2017

- Management of Bangalore-based software developers
- Testing of Simply's CRM system pre and post launch

IT PROJECT MANAGER & COMMS. LEAD

Boardmeter | STARTUP | 2016 – 2018

- IT P.M., business dev. strategy, interim CEO '17 '18
- Onboarding and evaluation of high-profile companies

OTHER

CONTENT CREATOR @ <u>Talentguiden</u> | FREDERIKSBERG | 16 Company portrait articles

PRESIDENT @ CBS Code | FREDERIKSBERG | 19 – Front-end development | Fundraising & partnership lead

VOLUNTEER @ Finn Nørgaard Foreningen | KBH K | 18 – Front-end development | Content creation | Event staff

VOLUNTEER @ TEDxCopenhagen | KBH K | 19 IT staff | Event staff



CONTACT

+45 24 24 29 69

nicolaibthomsen@gmail.com

DK-2000 Frederiksberg

<u>LinkedIn</u>

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE (2016 – 2019)

BA. & Information Technology

Copenhagen Business School | GPA: 9.5 5TH Semester @ San Diego State University

CURRENT (2019 - 2021)

MSc. BA & IT – Data Science

Copenhagen Business School

CERTIFICATIONS

ITIL® Foundation V3 | Boost.ai® Advanced Al Trainer | Boost.ai® Al Trainer | (Udemy)

EXTRACURRICULAR COURSES

TENSORFLOW FOR DEEP LEARNING

TensorFlow / Keras | Udemy | 2019

PYTHON FOR DATA SCIENCE AND MACHINE LEARNING BOOTCAMP

Python / SK-Learn | Udemy | 2019

WINDOWS PROGRAMMING

C# | San Diego State University | 2018

COMPLETE C# MASTERCLASS

C# / LINQ | Udemy | 2018

COMPLETE JAVASCRIPT COURSE

JavaScript | Udemy | 2017

COMPLETE JAVA MASTERCLASS

Java | Udemy | 2017